I'm Lizz and I'm the CEO and Founder of PO' UP!
Card Game, Party Game Celebrating Black Experiences from College to the Workplace.
I'm going to talk a little bit about my experience selling on Amazon, specifically my tips for getting
started if you are a new seller.
Now, if you are new to Amazon, make sure you have your own website set up.
This shows that you not only are ready to sell on Amazon, but this allows you to get used to selling
on your own platform, managing orders.
All of these insider tips are going to help you as you learn how to navigate the back end of Amazon.
Once you have your URL up and running, the next step is seeing if you qualify for any additional
certifications.
If you are a black owned business or you are a woman owned business, you will want to upload those
certifications into Amazon so you can have a badge that says, "I'm a woman owned business.
I am a black owned business and supplier gateway is a really easy tool for getting the certification."
Once you have your URL, it takes just a few minutes of your time to sign up and it's very affordable.
Once you have the certification, you can go on Amazon's website to get set up for selling and I
highly recommend opting into the fulfillment by Amazon program, FBA.
FBA is super important because it takes the logistics out of running your Amazon account.
This means all you have to do is package up your inventory to ship to Amazon and Amazon will take
care of the rest.
When orders come in on Amazon, Amazon's warehouse will ship those orders out directly to your customer.
For me specifically, I recommend starting small and testing out how much product you are able to
sell on Amazon before you increase the amount of inventory that you ship to Amazon's warehouse.
Those are my initial tips for getting ready to sell on Amazon and opting into fulfillment by Amazon,
also known as Amazon's FBA program.